Ever since last night,
I've had this weird feeling that there's
something important I have to do.
But I can't remember what.
Oh, man.
Why do my shoes and bag feel
heavier than usual today?
Hold on.
This house!
How strange.
Somehow I ended up walking all
the way back to Rohan's house.
The door's open.
I'd like to drop in and thank him for
being such a great host yesterday.
But I'll be late for school.
I probably shouldn't.
Being an artist, he's
probably still asleep.
He'd be rude to just barge in.
I really shouldn't.
Rohan.
He's working with such
a chilling expression.
And for some reason,
I can't shake the feeling that being
in this house is actually terrifying.
But why?
You finally made it.
It's good to see you.
You're right on time. Huh?
Sorry, but could I ask you to
wait there for just a moment?
Two more pages and next week's
manuscript will be complete.
It'll only take about 20 minutes or so.
Did he say he could finish
two pages in 20 minutes?
That can't be right.
I must have misheard him.
He couldn't possibly draw two pages from
scratch in such a short amount of time.
And they're for next week?
When we were here yesterday, he just finished
drawing the manuscript for this week.
Whoa!
He used the pen right off the bat!
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
How can he ink such complex
drawings without sketching first?
Whoa,
he's not hesitating at all and is even
hammering out the
backgrounds at the same time!
His hand movement was so quick!
I didn't even have a chance
to make out what he did!
No way!
He's beta-coloring by flicking the ink
around like perfectly aimed shuriken,
and somehow he's not leaving
a single stray mark behind!
His technique is incredible!
To beta-color without a brush takes an
amount of skill I've never seen before!
You've gotta be kidding!
He's already done?
It only took him about two minutes
to finish all the beta-coloring.
And it's all thanks to you, Koichi.
I am overflowing with creative energy.
My body hungers for more.
I have to keep drawing.
Finishing 19 pages in one night has
been an experience like no other.
At this very moment, a
masterpiece is forming.
Your life is astonishing.
I don't get it.
What is this?
Get cracking!
I want the next reality from your past.
Hurry and show me your next page!
I'm aware that your weight decreases
with every page I liberate,
but you don't mind, do you?
It's a small price to pay
for becoming a masterpiece!
Immortalized for all eternity!
I remember!
His power is heaven's door!
Rohan, you're one of
the enemy's stand-users!
Thank you.
I'll change you!
Well now!
I know it's not done just yet,
but this single panel could
be a book hauled by itself!
Fantastic!
I feel like I'm maturing, both as
a manga artist and a stand user!
And now to read this page.
Interesting.
Unless I'm mistaken.
That's Shining Diamond's Josuke
Higashikata, and the Han's Okuyasu Nijimura.
But this doesn't make any sense.
Why would they show up on
my doorstep out of the blue?
There's just no way Koichi would
have mentioned me to the two of them.
What's going on here?
Huh?
I don't know how, but
it's Josuke and Okuyasu!
When I didn't show up for school,
they must have noticed I was
missing and tracked me down!
I have to get them to save me!
I'm almost there!
If I can just open the door, they can
rush in and get me out of this place!
Huh?
Oh, hey!
This is such a surprise!
What are you two doing here?
And for that matter,
how do you even find me?
I'll let it be.
Josuke and Okuyasu don't really
interest me at the moment.
For now, I'll finish up the
last two pages for next week,
and then I'll procure even
more material from Koichi.
I can hardly contain myself.
You came here to watch a
manga artist do his work?
How can this guy afford to
work in such a nice place?
Rohan Kishibe.
Is he famous or something?
Ever heard of him, Josuke?
I'm not that well-versed in manga.
In fact, Hazamada bitched at me for
not knowing anything about Perman.
Wait, what?
That wasn't even remotely close
to what I wanted to say to them.
Why am I blanking all of a sudden?
Well,
we saw you staggering around, so we thought
it would be a good idea to tell you.
But it seems like everything is Aqua.
I guess we'll leave you to it.
Thanks a lot!
What?
Do you want to come inside
and observe with me?
Nah, thanks for the offer, though.
Being around famous
people makes me nervous.
Same, just knowing that
you weren't in there?
fooling around with
some smoking hot chick!
is enough for me, so I'm out.
See you later, Koichi. Bye.
Why can't I remember what I wanted to say?
I'm sure I was trying to tell them
something really important, but what was it?
Now I remember what I wanted to say!
I needed them to rescue me!
Yusuke, okuyasu, wait!
See you guys at school in a bit. Kay.
Make sure you're not late.
I won't be.
What was that?
That's not what I wanted to say at all!
Dammit!
I'm not able to ask my friends for help!
We've never gone up against
a stand this terrifying.
It's invincible.
I don't think we have nearly
enough power to beat Heaven's door.
Ah, I see now.
At the rate he's going,
he's going to rip out all my experiences
and leave me a lifeless husk.
I sense an infiltrator
has entered the mansion.
What did you do while you were downstairs?
Answer me.
Ah! Ah!
Okuyasu!
Hold it right there!
Just keep looking straight ahead, buddy!
You'd better not try anything funny,
or I'll crush you with my
stand, you doodling dipshit!
I don't know how you
figured out I was in danger,
Okuyasu, but thank goodness you're here!
You're the best!
It appears as though your friend
had a sudden epiphany, Koichi.
I didn't notice it before,
but that small cut on your hand must have
given away the predicament
you're currently in.
You probably scratched yourself on
something while you were crawling.
I was so focused on
escaping, I didn't notice!
That is what gave it away, right, Okuyasu?
And your stand is the hand.
Also, you have a bit of a complex
regarding your dead brother, Keicho.
And whenever you try to
make a difficult decision,
you wish your brother was
there to do it for you.
Isn't that right?
Who the hell told you all that?
Speak up, punk!
Hey, Koichi, tell me everything
about this guy's stand.
Yeah, he's able to!
I can't do it!
I can't say anything that
put Rohan at a disadvantage!
If you catch a glimpse of
even one panel, it's all over!
I desperately want to
tell you not to look!
Please, don't look at that manga!
Hold it!
Didn't I tell you not to move a muscle?
Okuyasu,
you were of no concern to me at first,
but that changed the moment
you entered this house.
Now you'll serve as another of my muses.
Bastard!
What the hell?
He's really fast!
Okuyasu!
What's going on?
Josuke Higashikata, I know
you're hiding over there.
Okuyasu!
What the hell is up with
this freaky-ass manga artist?
Silence.
Now then, Koichi, if you
don't mind, I have a question.
Why do you think Josuke Higashikata is
choosing to remain hidden behind that door?
Hmm?
So what do you think?
Why won't he show himself, Koichi?
Well, if I had to guess,
I'd say he's laying low so he won't
accidentally catch a sight of your manga!
My thought's exactly
how very astute of you.
Okuyasu knew nothing about
the power of my Heaven's Door,
so he fell from my trap
hook, line, and sinker.
But in doing so, he exposed the
true nature of my stand to Josuke,
causing him to take cover.
I feel that I am somewhat...
No, at this point it would appear
I'm at a significant disadvantage.
However, I believe that Josuke has an
ulterior motive for choosing to remain hidden.
What do you think that is?
At any rate, this game of cat and
mouse has gone on long enough.
I suppose I'll have to resort to other
means to smoke him out of his hiding place.
He's only hiding because he wants to
figure out the best way to kick your ass!
You're probably right about that.
But that wasn't the
answer I was looking for.
No matter, though, I think I've got it.
Our dear hero Josuke is
contemplating whether
he should flee the mansion
all by his lonesome...
some friend he is.
You're wrong!
Josuke would never leave us behind!
Right you are, Koichi. Huh?
According to your files,
Josuke Higashikata has
far too much character
to even think about abandoning you two.
But due to the dynamic nature
of a manga artist's work,
they tend to consider every
conceivable possibility?
at every conceivable moment.
So in the situation we
now find ourselves in,
what course of action will
our protagonist employ?
Let's see.
Perhaps Josuke could flee with
knowledge of my stand's power,
which would be quite the dilemma for me.
You know, running away might
be the best thing he could do!
He could go and get Jotaro!
And if he told Yukako
what happened to you,
I'm sure she'd be angry
enough to help us out.
I'd rather not see her again.
But we could use her hair.
Josuke, get out of here and
tell them what's going on!
You imbeciles!
I explained all of that to you
exactly so it wouldn't happen.
And I doubt you'd be so quick to prompt
Josuke if you knew what was written in you.
Koichi, I'm giving you my express permission
to explain the content of my missive.
Let's hear it.
There's no way!
You can't be serious!
Hey, out with it.
What did he write, Koichi?
How can he do that? It's sick.
He's completely trapped
us in this mansion.
It doesn't matter what we do,
we're never getting out of here.
Man, that's why I'm asking what the
hell this sickle run on my arm, Koichi.
Burn myself to death?
That's why I said we're
never getting out of here.
You'll kill yourself if Josuke so
much as lifts a finger to help us.
Hey, wait a second.
He thinks I'll burn myself to death?
That's total crazy talk!
As if I'd ever do something as
messed up as setting myself on!
That's just it, you will!
We're completely incapable of defying him!
Come on, right hand, knock it off!
This is so wrong!
So you've come out.
Like he really had a choice!
He was basically dragged out of here
because he couldn't bear to hear us suffer.
Oh, that's a rather childish move.
But closing your eyes could be effective.
There's nowhere to run
in this cramped room.
If he managed to knock me out?
Heaven's Door would release its grip.
and Okuyasu wouldn't commit suicide.
Josuke, help!
Closing his eyes is simple-minded,
but it just might work.
As long as he doesn't see the
manuscript, Heaven's Door is powerless.
Come on, keep charging.
Hmm, a pretty good plan.
But all I have to do now is find
a way to force your eyes open.
Think fast!
What's this?
He's powering through the pain.
If he keeps charging at
me like a stampeding bull,
things are going to get very ugly.
If I were a manga protagonist,
what would I do in this situation?
How would I get my enemy to open his eyes?
Keep going, Josuke!
Repeat, think, hurry up!
That's it.
Surely something in Koichi's
file will be able to help.
There!
Exactly what I needed!
It seems certain comments set you
off, such as your hair is laughable.
Or wasn't that pincushion on your
head in fashion like two decades ago?
Or maybe you think that
hair looks cool, don't you?
How's that?
I guess remarks like those
really do set him off.
I must admit it's hard to believe,
but the files are always accurate.
What a preposterous Achilles' heel.
What the hell?
Did you say? Huh?
Just take it easy, Josuke!
I dare you to insult my hair again!
If you insist.
Fine.
Here goes.
You might think your hair looks cool,
but in actuality, it may
be the shittiest hairstyle!
I've ever had the misfortune
of laying eyes upon!
Though to be fair?
That nest atop your useless noggin!
and may come in handy should a
pigeon come by and decide to roost.
But that's a very strong may.
Now witness heaven's door!
I win.
Point!
How the...
How is this happening?
I'm certain his eyes were open and he
got a full flash of the manuscript!
So why hasn't my
stanzibility taken effect?
We're back to normal! You're right!
I know I showed him the page. So what?
Where the hell did you slither off to?
Get out of here, you punk bitch!
Hey, I don't think he can
see straight right now.
Can't see?
Hold on, are you trying to
say Rohan's stupid insults?
Worked him up so much that he
doesn't even realize what he's doing?
Come on out, you manga-obsessed asshole!
I got a story for you!
It doesn't matter if it's from
a comic or someone's mouth.
If he hears any kind of hair
insult, he flies into a blind rage.
Incredible!
I had no idea his temper was this bad.
I don't think I've seen anything
like this in my entire life.
What the hell?
This is a facet of Josuke's personality
that even Koichi knew nothing about,
so it wasn't in his file
like everything else.
Though I still don't get it.
Why does he get so upset over his hair?
There has to be a reason.
But what is it?
Whoever insults my hair will
get the full brunt of my fury.
I won't stand for that bullshit!
Now that I think about it,
I'm positive Josuke told
me the reason behind his
freak-outs when it comes to
people insulting his hair,
but it's kind of an involved story.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
It all happened when Josuke
was a little kid, and uh...
I'll try to remember
the story as best I can,
but I might have to fill
in some gaps along the way.
Josuke was 4 years old, and he'd passed
out from an inexplicably high fever.
For 50 days, no one knew
whether he would live or die.
Josuke
He found out later on that all of this
happened right around the time Jotaro and Mr.
Joestar were in Egypt
They traveled there in
order to defeat a heinous
stand user named Dio.
Josuke's mom had no
idea what was happening?
So she loaded him in the car and headed to
a hospital in S-City as fast as she could.
But at the time, Morioh was in the
middle of its worst blizzard in 18 years.
No use.
What do I do?
Nobody ever uses this back road anymore.
And there's not a damn payphone in sight.
I'm an idiot.
I should have called for an ambulance.
Why did I bring Josuke out in the snow?
What's wrong with me?
And that's when it happened.
Hey, what the hell do you want?
Just go away, you creeper!
Got it.
Thank you so much!
Eventually,
his mom tried to search for the young man,
but she couldn't find any trace of him.
While the stranger may not have
personally saved his life that night,
as far as four-year-old
Josuke was concerned,
that young man he encountered was a hero
unlike anyone he'd ever seen before.
He became Josuke's role
model and a shining
example of what it means
to be a good person.
When someone insults that part of him, it
triggers something deep inside his heart.
I still don't know who
he is or where he's from.
But in honor of him coming to our
rescue, I decided to adopt his hairstyle.
No one is allowed to disrespect
it, no matter who they are.
Disrespecting my hair
means disrespecting him.
As far as I'm aware, that's the
reason he flies off the handle.
But I have to admit, I thought
Josuke was just making it up,
so I wasn't listening very carefully.
Huh.
I've never heard that story.
Careful!
Rohan's holding a pen! You master!
Don't know when to call it quits, do ya?
No, that's not it.
I wanted to make sure I wrote down that
beautiful story before I lost consciousness.
What a tale. Bravo.
I had an amazing experience to boot.
I'm overjoyed.
Experiences like this
happen once in a lifetime.
Such great inspiration.
How lucky am I.
I'm so glad I packed my bags and
moved to Morioh. It's no use.
As long as he's alive, he'll keep
searching for manga material,
even if he ends up battered and bruised.
At this point, you have to
commend his determination.
Putting aside good and bad for a minute,
he has one of the most admirable
work ethics I've ever seen.
Rohan-sensei is truly
a super manga artist.
I finally found you, manga artist!
Last I checked, I wasn't
done punching you!
His determination is
pretty commendable, too.
Um, yeah.
Due to an unforeseen illness,
Rohan Kishibe's Pink Dark Boy
will be on hiatus for one month.
Get closer, breathe in
and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you.
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I
need you, but ooh, I gotta find you.
Ooh,
I want you, I don't know if I need
you, but ooh, I gotta find you.
SmackDown!